eschoolsolutions.com 2017-09-19

# Privacy Policy | TalentEd - Data-driven K-12 Talent Management Solutions

This policy covers how PeopleAdmin, Inc. handles and uses personal information that we collect when you visit and interact with our web site. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

## Information Collection and Use

PeopleAdmin, Inc. collects personal information when you request an account with PeopleAdmin, Inc., when you request information or register for events. We ask for information such as your name, telephone number, email address, occupation, and employer. When you register with PeopleAdmin, Inc. and sign in to our site, you are not anonymous to us.

PeopleAdmin, Inc. automatically receives and records information from your computer and browser, including your IP address, cookie information, software and hardware attributes, and the pages you visit.

PeopleAdmin, Inc. uses the information we collect to fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, and contact you.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

PeopleAdmin, Inc. does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies.

We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process (such as law enforcement requests), or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of PeopleAdmin, Inc.’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

## Cookies

PeopleAdmin, Inc. may set and access PeopleAdmin cookies on your computer.

## Confidentiality and Security

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need access to that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.

PeopleAdmin utilizes industry standard technology to secure customer information including the use of SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption in transferring client data; multi-level firewalls to prevent external intrusion; frequent backups of customer data; and a fully redundant hardware platform to ensure system availability.

## Changes to this Policy

PeopleAdmin, Inc. may update this policy at any time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your PeopleAdmin, Inc. account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

## Acceptance

By using this web site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree with the terms and conditions contained in this policy, please do not use the site.

## Questions and Suggestions

If you have thoughts, questions or suggestions about PeopleAdmin’s privacy policy, please contact us at [info@peopleadmin.com](mailto:info@peopleadmin.com).

￼
